[
  {
    "Q1": {
      "question": "What is the longest that an elephant has ever lived? (That we know of)",
      "answer1": "17 Years",
      "answer2": "49 Years",
      "answer3": "86 Years",
      "answer4": "142 Years",
      "correct": "answer3"
    },
    "Q2": {
      "question": "How many rings are on the Olympic flag?",
      "answer1": "none",
      "answer2": "4",
      "answer3": "5",
      "answer4": "7",
      "correct": "answer3"
    },
    "Q3": {
      "question": "What is a tarsier?",
      "answer1": "a primate",
      "answer2": "a lizard",
      "answer3": "a mammal",
      "answer4": "a fish",
      "correct": "answer1"
    },
    "Q4": {
      "question": "How did Spider-Man get his powers?",
      "answer1": "Military experiment gone awry",
      "answer2": "Born with them",
      "answer3": "Woke up with them after a strange dream",
      "answer4": "Bitten by a radioactive spider",
      "correct": "answer4"
    },
    "Q5": {
      "question": "In darts, what's the most points you can score with a single throw?",
      "answer1": "20",
      "answer2": "50",
      "answer3": "60",
      "answer4": "100",
      "correct": "answer3"
    },
    "Q6": {
      "question": "Which of these animals does NOT appear in the Chinese zodiac?",
      "answer1": "Bear",
      "answer2": "Rabbit",
      "answer3": "Dragon",
      "answer4": "Dog",
      "correct": "answer1"
    },
    "Q7": {
      "question": "Who are known as Brahmins?",
      "answer1": "Surfers in California",
      "answer2": "Members of India's highest caste",
      "answer3": "The government of Thailand",
      "answer4": "Its a totally made-up word",
      "correct": "answer2"
    },
    "Q8": {
      "question": "How many holes are on a standard bowling ball?",
      "answer1": "2",
      "answer2": "3",
      "answer3": "5",
      "answer4": "10",
      "correct": "answer2"
    },
    "Q9": {
      "question": "What are the main colors on the flag of Spain?",
      "answer1": "Black and Yellow",
      "answer2": "Orange and Green",
      "answer3": "Red and Yellow",
      "answer4": "Blue and White",
      "correct": "answer3"
    },
    "Q10": {
      "question": "In the nursery rhyme, how many blackbirds were baked in a pie?",
      "answer1": "4",
      "answer2": "11",
      "answer3": "24",
      "answer4": "99",
      "correct": "answer3"
    }
  }
]